

Nicolai Medbo

Profile

I'm a recently graduated IT student with experience in design, installation, testing and maintenance of software systems. Throughout my studies I have been equipped with a diverse and promising skill-set. Proficient in various platforms, languages, and embedded systems. I'm familiar with industry standard development tools and procedures. I'm able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

Employment History

Store Employee at CEWE Japan Photo, Oslo

October 2022 — Present

As a Store Employee at CEWE Japan Photo, I am responsible for providing excellent customer service and ensuring the smooth operation of the store. I assist customers with their inquiries, provide product information, and ensure a pleasant printing experience. My role also involves camera troubleshooting, photography advice and printing assistance.

Software Engineer at Iver Norge AS, Oslo

January 2024 — June 2024

I worked on developing a CMDB (customer management database) for managing azure client data. We utilized a spring boot backend, along with a vue is frontend and a noSQL azure cosmos database.

My role also involved agile methodologies, such as scrum organization, team meetings and general team structure.

Main accomplishments:

- Successfully working in an agile environment following scrum principles
- · Completing a certified scrum master course
- Developing a working back-end that processes and sorts all azure customer data
- Making a front-end web app to visually display the data

Details

OSLO, Norway, +47 41516419

Tenico05@gmail.com

Skills

TypeScript

JavaScript

HTML

Java

Git

SQL

Technical Troubleshooting

System Integration

Software Development

C#

Arduino

Python

React

Hobbies

· Implementing multithreading

Education

IT-Programming Bachelor, Høyskolen Kristiania

August 2021 — June 2024

My hobbies are a bit mixed, I have some tech related ones and some not. I run my own small scale 3D printing business, which involves tinkering and customer interactions. I play videogames and build drones. I also enjoy playing golf, kitesurfing and photography!

Languages

Norwegian

English